/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data2A_1', {
    title: '2A.1 Translating Words to Math',
    path: '2A.1-translating-words-to-math',
    children: [{
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{74 is greater than 26}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 74 > 26}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 26 < 74}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 74 - 26}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 74 + 26}}}}}',
                answer: 'A',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{A: 74 > 26}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{9 is less than 23}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 9 - 23}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 9 < 23}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 9 + 23}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 23 > 9}}}}}',
                answer: 'B',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{B: 9 < 23}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{5 is more than 1}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 1 < 5}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 5 > 1}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 1 + 5}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 5 - 1}}}}}',
                answer: 'B',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{B: 5 > 1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{82 is how much less than 98?}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 82 + 98}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 98 > 82}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 98 - 82}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 82 < 98}}}}}',
                answer: 'C',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{C: 98 - 82}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{91 is more than 66}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 66 + 91}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 66 < 91}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 91 - 66}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 91 > 66}}}}}',
                answer: 'D',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{D: 91 > 66}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{13 is how much more than 12?}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 13 > 12}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 12 < 13}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 12 + 13}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 13 - 12}}}}}',
                answer: 'D',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{D: 13 - 12}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{28 is more than 16}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 16 < 28}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 28 > 16}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 16 + 28}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 28 - 16}}}}}',
                answer: 'B',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{B: 28 > 16}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{45 is greater than 1}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 1 < 45}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 45 > 1}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 45 - 1}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 1 + 45}}}}}',
                answer: 'B',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{B: 45 > 1}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{28 is how much less than 47?}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 47 - 28}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 28 < 47}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 47 > 28}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 28 + 47}}}}}',
                answer: 'A',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{A: 47 - 28}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Translating Words to Math',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\butgrp{\\col{\\row{\\str{Translate the following words into a math expression or an inequality statement:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\str{6 is less than 73}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\but{A}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 6 + 73}}}{\\row{\\but{B}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 73 > 6}}}{\\row{\\but{C}{F}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 73 - 6}}}{\\row{\\but{D}{T}}{\\str{\xA0 \xA0 6 < 73}}}}}',
                answer: 'D',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{D: 6 < 73}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
